Sanrio Inc. C-TPAT Supply Chain Security Profile 						
Process Owners:			"Facility A: 570 Eccles Ave. So. San Francisco, CA 94080.                           Facility B: 990 West 190th ST, Suite # 220, Torrance, CA 90502.             Facility C: One Bridge Plaza, Suite # 470, Fort Lee, NJ 07024."			
		S = Security         HR = Human Resources          P = Purchasing       D = Info. Tech                           W = Warehouse        T = Traffic                          I = Import     				
			Facilities			
 		Sections/Questions	Facility A	Facility B	Facility C	Procedure Reference
	#	Facility Overview				
S	1	"What type of activities are performed at this facility? (i.e. manufacturing=M, storage=S, distribution = D )  "	"Operations, Storage, Dsitribution "	Sales Only	Sales Only 	
S	2	What are the hours of operation for the facility?	7AM - 6 PM	9 AM- 5 PM 	9 AM - 5 PM	
S	3	"Provide a brief description of each facility including: property, buildings, fencing, other barriers, location of security office.  Provide drawings when available."	see outline	Commercial Building	Commercial Building	
S	4	Does the facility have a security policy/statement?	Yes	Yes	Yes	
		Physical Security - Security Guards				
S	5	Are there security guards on premises?  	"No but we have personnel in charge of security in the warehouse, office and parking lot"	Yes as provided and contracted to Professional Services by the Building owner 	Yes as provided and contracted to Professional Services by the Building owner 	
S	6	Security guards present 24/7?	no	n/a 	n/a 	
S	7	Security Violation Reporting procedures in place?	yes	n/a 	n/a 	
S	8	"If applicable, what is name of the Security Service provider?  "	n/a	n/a 	n/a 	
S	9	What are the qualifications required of Security Personnel?	n/a	n/a 	n/a 	
S	10	Are Security Personnel armed?	no 	n/a 	n/a 	
S	11	What kind of continuing education is required of Security Personnel?	Training procedures 	n/a 	n/a 	
S	12	"Is scope of their responsibilities defined and documented?  If so, obtain document.      "	no 	n/a 	n/a 	
		Physical Security - Fencing				
S	13	Is there an exterior perimeter fence?   	yes	n/a 	n/a 	PHY 005
S	14	What is the height of the fence?	8'	n/a 	n/a 	PHY 005
S	15	When and how are fences inspected for integrity and damage?	Warehouse Rec'g Personnel inspects the fence daily for damage or tampering and notifies the Dist manager if any problem	n/a 	n/a 	PHY 005
S	16	"Is interior fencing used to segregate domestic, international, high value and hazardous cargo?"	No except for high value merchandise	n/a 	n/a 	
		Physical Security - Gatehouse				
S	17	Is there a gatehouse?   	Yes			
S	18	How many gatehouses for each facility?	1			
S	19	Is gatehouse operated 24/7?  	no			
		Physical Security - Parking				
S	20	Is there an employee/visitor only parking area?   	Yes			PHY 007
S	21	"Is access to the parking area controlled?   If controlled, please explain in outline.    "	Yes			PHY 007
S	22	Is the parking area monitored by surveillance cameras?	Yes			PHY 007
S	23	Is the parking area subject to roving security patrols?	Yes			PHY 007
S	24	Are parking decals or passes utilized?  	No			
		Physical Security - Building Structures				
S	25	Are buildings constructed of materials that resist unlawful entry	Yes			PHY 008
S	26	When and how are buildings inspected for integrity and damage?	Daily inspection done by Office Services and immediate repair done if necessary. 			PHY 008
S	27	Are restricted areas clearly marked?	Yes			PHY 008
		Physical Security - Internal Restricted Areas				
S	28	Are there restricted access locations within any of the buildings?	Yes			PHY 008
S	29	"How is access restricted?  Security Guard, Key Card, Locks"	"Electronic locks, keypad & alarm"			PHY 008
		Physical Security - Locking Devices				
S	30	Do adequate locking devices protect external and internal doors & windows?	Yes			PHY 009
S	31	What controls are in place to control issuance of locks and keys?	Management controls			PHY 009
S	32	"Are locks inspected for maintenance, repair, testing, etc?"	Yes			PHY 009
		Physical Security - Lighting				
S	33	Is adequate lighting provided for the following?                                            ·Entrances and  Exits                                                                                          ·Cargo handling and storage areas                                                                    ·Fence lines                                                                                                                ·Parking Areas	Yes			PHY 010
S	34	Is there an emergency lighting system/generator?	Yes			PHY 010
		Physical Security - Alarms/Cameras				
S	35	Does the facility have an alarm system?	Yes			PHY 011
S	36	Does an outside company monitor the alarms or are they monitored by internal security personnel?	Alarms are monitored by internal security personnel 			PHY 011
S	37	"What type of mechanism is used to alert a breach?  Audible, Visual, Pager, Other"	Audible			PHY 011
S	38	Does the alarm alert security personnel?	Yes			PHY 011
S	39	Does the alarm alert local law enforcement?	Yes			PHY 011
S	40	Does the facility utilize CCTV cameras?  	Yes			PHY 011
S	41	"If CCTV cameras are utilized, are they continuously monitored?    "	Yes			PHY 011
S	42	Are CCTV's recorded?	Yes			PHY 011
S	43	Are CCTV recordings retained for more than 7 days?	Yes			PHY 011
S	44	"Are video and alarm systems inspected for maintenance, repair, testing, etc?"	Yes			PHY 011
		Physical Access Controls - Employees				
S	45	Does the company issue badges to employees?	yes			ACC 001
S	46	"Are the badges color coded to designate access privileges, etc?"	No			
S	47	Are employees required to show an identification badge when entering the premises?	No			
S	48	"Does the company have procedures for issuance, removal and changing of employee access devices?"	yes			ACC 001
S	49	"Does the company have a policy for searching employees, vehicles and personal effects?"	yes			ACC 006
		Physical Access Controls - Visitors				
S	50	"Are visitors identified & controlled through a tracking system?  If yes, please explain method of identification and control in outline.  "	Yes			ACC 002 & 003
S	51	Are visitor records or logs kept?  	Yes			ACC 002 & 003
S	52	Are visitors escorted while on the premises?	yes			ACC 002 & 003
S	53	Are visitors subject to search?	yes			ACC 006
S	54	What type of identification are visitors required to submit for identification?	"Photo ID, Business card"			ACC 002 & 003
S	55	"Is there use of visitor passes, badge identification system?"	Yes			ACC 002 & 003
		Physical Access Controls - Deliveries				
S	56	"If facility contains a loading dock, is access to loading/unloading area controlled?  (Please explain method of control in outline.  Method documented?) "	Yes			
S	57	Do delivery drivers display identification?  What type?	Company Uniform w/ name tag			
S	58	"If deemed necessary, is company affiliation verified?       "	Yes			
S	59	Is incoming or outgoing mail periodically screened before dissemination?	Yes			
S	60	Are vehicles subject to inspection upon entering and/or exiting the premises?	Yes			
S	61	Do passenger vehicles and commercial carriers use the same entrances and exits?	Yes except for Receiving area			
S	62	Is access to the facility limited to certain time periods?	Yes			
		Physical Access Controls - Challenging/Removing Unauthorized Persons				
S	63	"What procedures are in place to identify, challenge and address unauthorized/unidentified persons?"	see outline			
		Personnel Security - Pre-employment verification				
HR	64	Are pre-employment screening and background reviews conducted?                                                                     ·Application - References - Verification of past employment                              ·Criminal History                                                                                                 ·Credit 	Yes			
HR	65	Are prospective employees subject to drug and/or alcohol testing?	Yes			PER 001
HR	66	Does the company verify citizenship on new employees?	Yes			PER 003
HR	67	Does the company hire contract labor?  What policies are applied to contract laborers?	"Yes, same as Employee policy"			
		Personnel Security - Periodic Checks				
HR	68	Are employees subject to drug and/or alcohol testing?	No			
HR	69	Are periodic background checks done on employees in sensitive positions or for cause?	Yes			
HR	70	Do internal code(s) of conduct exist?	Yes			
		Personnel Security - Termination Procedures				
HR	71	Do internal controls exist for reporting and managing problems related to personnel security? 	Yes			PER 006 & 007
HR	72	"Does the company have procedures in place to remove identification, facility and system access for terminated employees?"	Yes			PER 008
		Information Technology				
D	73	Does the company use individualized access accounts?	Yes			TEC 001
D	74	Are passwords used and required to be changed periodically?	Yes			TEC 001
D	75	"Are passwords required to incorporate letters, number and symbols or other formatting to prevent hackers from decoding the passwords?"	Yes			TEC 001
D	76	"Is a system in place to identify improper access, tampering or altering of business data?"	Yes			TEC 005
D	77	"Is physical security provided for servers, phone systems and other computer controlled devices?  "	Yes			TEC 002
D	78	Are processes in place for backup of computer data?  Where are the backup copies stored?	"Yes, copies stored in a Tape Drive in a restricted and locked room"			TEC 002
D	79	"Are firewalls, spam filters, virus protection, spy ware and other software programs used?"	Yes			TEC 005
D	80	Are systems protected from power interruptions by a generator?	Yes			TEC 005
D	81	Are employees informed of internet and email usage policies?	Yes			TEC 003 & 004
D	82	Are systems in place to monitor internet and email for abuse?	Yes			TEC 003 & 004
		Procedural Security - Shipping and Receiving				
S	83	"Are delivery personnel required to have company identification, including photo identification, prior to acceptance of their cargo?    "	Yes			ACC 005
S	84	What type of access to facilities do delivery personnel have?	Limited to the loading/unloading area during delivery or pick-up			ACC 005
W	85	Do receiving personnel have advance notice of cargo arrival?	Yes			PRO 002
W	86	Is cargo immediately unloaded and received into the warehouse?	Yes			PRO 002
W	87	Are receiving documents generated & used to verify cargo at time of acceptance? 	Yes			PRO 002
W	88	"Is piece count, shipment identification labels, descriptions and country of origin verified against shipping documents?"	Yes			"PRO 005, 006"
W	89	Are overage and shortage reports generated?  Who are they reported to?	"Yes, distributed to Import Dept, Mdse Control, Acctg, Vendor"			"PRO 005, 006"
W	90	"If signs of tampering or damage to carton/crate are evident, are there procedures in place to investigate and report?   "	Yes			PRO 002
W	91	Is any cargo stored outside?  How is the outdoor area secured?	No			
W	92	"Once cargo is accepted, is it stored in secure manner to prevent unauthorized tampering?"	Yes			
W	93	"If there is hazardous cargo, is it labeled and stored separately?"	No hazardous cargo handled			
W	94	Is import/export/domestic cargo segregated during storage?	Yes			
W	95	"If cargo arrives in ocean containers, are seal numbers verified prior to opening?"	Yes			PRO 002
W	96	"If exporting cargo utilizing ocean containers, are seals placed and numbers recorded prior to departure from company docking facility?    "	Yes			CON 001
W	97	Is the cargo receiving/dock area restricted to unauthorized personnel? 	Yes			PRO 002
S	98	"If applicable, is the “docking” area patrolled by security personnel? "	Yes			
W	99	Does the company have procedures in place to ensure the products shipped are properly packaged and secure?	Yes			PRO 001
W	100	What types of shipping documents are created?	"Invoice, Packing list, B/L, Manifest"			
W/HR	101	What types of procedures/training are in place for warehouse safety?	"IIPP (Injury and Illness Prevention Program), C-TPAT Procedures and Training"			IIPP/ C-TPAT TRA procedures
		Procedural Security - Documentation				
I	102	"Are procedures in place to ensure all information required in clearing of cargo is legible, complete, accurate and reported in a  timely manner?"	Yes			PRO 010
I	103	Do desks and file cabinets have locking devices?	Yes			
I	104	How are Customs documents stored?	"in locked metal file cabinets, boxed/taped then stored in warehouse, Electronic file"			
I	105	How long are Customs documents maintained?	8 years			PRO 008
		Education and Training -  General Security Issues				
S/HR	106	Are procedures in place for communicating with law enforcement officials outside of the company?	Yes			
S/HR	107	Are procedures in place for communicating with security departments in other facilities?	No			
S/HR	108	Do employees receive training on security awareness and procedures?	Yes			
S/HR	109	Is there an employee policy manual?	Yes			
	 	Do employees receive training on the following topics?				
S/HR	110	Facilities security?	Yes			PRO 013
S/HR	111	Theft prevention?	Yes			TRA 005
S/HR	112	Information security controls?	Yes			"TEC 001, 002"
S/HR	113	Workplace Violence?	Yes			PER 07/ IIPP
S/HR	114	Sexual Harassment	Yes			PER 006
S/HR	115	Do internal controls exist for reporting and correcting employee misconduct? 	Yes			PER 005
S/HR	116	Do internal controls exist for reporting and correcting suspicious or illegal conduct? 	Yes			PER 005
S/HR	117	How are employees educated on security issues?                                                     ·Manuals                                                                                                          ·Internet                                                                                                     ·Classroom Training                                                                                       ·Bulletin Boards/Posters   	"Classroom Training, Manuals, Bulletin Boards"			TRA 003
		Education and Training -  International/Transportation/SCM				
HR/I	118	International Compliance - Import/Export?	Yes			TRA 002
HR/I/T/W	119	Cargo Security?	Yes			TRA 003
HR/T/W	120	Hazardous Materials?	Not handled 			
HR/I	121	C-TPAT?	Yes			"TRA 003, 004"
 		Education & Training - Potential Threats & Disasters				
S/HR	122	Does the company have a business continuity plan?	In process - to be completed by Sept 2007			
	 	Do employees receive training on the following topics?				
S/HR	123	Bomb Threats	Yes			IIPP
S/HR	124	Fires	Yes			IIPP
S/HR	125	"Severe Weather, including earthquakes and hurricanes"	Yes			DIS 006
S/HR	126	Personal Injury	Yes			IIPP
S/HR	127	Infectious Diseases	Yes			DIS 010
S/HR	128	Riots	No			
S/HR	129	Terrorist Attacks	Yes			DIS 001
S/HR	130	Does the company use evacuation drills?	Yes			DIS 003
		Conveyance Security - Seals				
P/T	131	Are all loaded containers bound for the U.S. sealed with high security seals meeting PAS ISO 17712 standards?	Yes			CON 001
P/T/W	132	Are written procedures in place stipulating how seals are to be controlled and affixed to loaded containers?	Yes			CON 001
P/T/W	133	Are written procedures in place for recognizing and reporting compromised seals and/or containers to CBP or other authorities?	Yes			"CON 001, 002"
		Conveyance Security - Container Inspection				
P/T/W	134	Are procedures in place to verify the physical integrity of containers prior to stuffing?	Yes			CON 002
P/T/W	135	Does the inspection process consist of the recommended 7-Point Inspection?                                                                                                                                                ·Front Wall                                                                                                                  ·Left Side                                                                                                            ·Right Side                                                                                                         ·Floor                                                                                                       ·Ceiling/Roof                                                                                           ·Inside/Outside Doors                                                                  ·Outside/Undercarriage                                                      	Yes			CON 002
T/W	136	Are procedures in place to verify the integrity of the container upon receipt?	Yes			CON 002
		Conveyance Security - Storage				
P/T/W	137	Are containers stored in a secure area to prevent unauthorized access? This includes all points in the supply chain from loading to unloading	Yes			"SEC 003, 004, 005, CON 002"
		Business Partners - Imports/Exports				
I	138	"Provide a list of Brokers used and indicate whether they are C-TPAT certified along with Address, Contact Party, Phone/Fax/Email information."	attachment PAR 001C			PAR 001C
I	139	What process/criteria is used in selecting brokers?  Provide written documentation.	attachment PAR 001			PAR 001C
I	140	Have the brokers completed a CBP Broker Supply Chain Questionnaire or similar document providing adequate information about the broker?	Yes			SEC 002B
I	141	How are security requirements communicated to brokers?	e-mail			"SEC 002, 002A, PAR 001"
I	142	Are brokers evaluated on a regular basis?	Yes 			PAR 001
		Business Partners - Traffic				
T	143	"Provide a list of Freight Forwarders and Carriers and indicate whether they are C-TPAT certified, along with Address, Contact Party, Phone/Fax/Email information.  "	attachment PAR 002B			PAR 002B
T	144	"What process/criteria is used in selecting Carriers, Forwarders, etc.  Provide written documentation."	attachment PAR 002			PAR 002
T	145	How are security requirements communicated to forwarders and carriers?	e-mail			"SEC 004, 004A, PAR 002"
T	146	"Have the air carriers, ocean carriers, truckers, and forwarders  completed a CBP Supply Chain Questionnaire or similar document providing adequate information about their business?"	Yes			"SEC 004B, PAR 002"
T	147	Are carriers and forwarders evaluated on a regular basis?	Yes			PAR 002
		"Business Partners - Manufacturers, Product Suppliers"				
P	148	What criteria is used to select suppliers?  Provide written procedures.	attachment PAR 003			PAR 003
P	149	Have the suppliers completed a CBP Supply Chain Security Questionnaire or similar document that provides adequate information about the supplier's business?	Yes			"SEC 003B, PAR 003"
P	150	How are security requirements communicated to suppliers?	"e-mail, letter"			"SEC 003, 003A, PAR 003"
C	151	Are security provisions included in supplier contracts?	Not yet - will start in Jan 2007			
P	152	"Provide list of top 25 foreign vendors based on dollar value and volume. Iinclude name, address, contact info, phone, fax, email, dollar value of purchases and number of shipments."	attachment - Top 25 vendors			
P	153	Are suppliers evaluated on a regular basis?	Yes			PAR 003
		Business Partners - Warehouse				
T/W 	154	"Are cargo storage facilities/warehouses utilized that are not Sanrio Inc facilities?   (If yes, please describe  services rendered,  name of company providing service, point(s) of contact to include name, telephone number, and e-mail address.  "	Yes - attachment PAR 004B			PAR 004B
T/W	155	"If applicable, are they C-TPAT certified?     "	No			
T/W	156	"Do they have a  documented security program in place?  If yes, then obtain copy."	Yes			SEC 005B
		C-TPAT Assessment Program				
S	157	Is there an annual security review?  Provide documentation	"Yes - attachment COM 001, 002"			"COM 001, 002"
Committee	158	Is there an annual C-TPAT review?  Provide documentation	"Yes - attachment COM 001, 002"			"COM 001, 002"
Committee	159	How and to whom are security/C-TPAT reviews communicated?	"C-TPAT Committee, Executive Management"			COM 001-003
Committee	160	Does the company have a security/CTPAT process improvement plan?	Yes			COM 003
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
						
